# **Hanif Aliffudin**

Jakarta Selatan, DKI Jakarta, 12410 | +62 8953 4233 7433 | hanifaliffudin@gmail.com linkedin.com/in/hanifaliffudin | hanifaliffudin.github.io/portfolio/

# **Objective**

Passionate Software Developer with 2+ years of experience in developing web and mobile applications. Skilled at writing clear, concise code that is easy to maintain and troubleshoot. Experienced in working with both small and large teams across multiple projects and companies. Able to work independently of remote locations or in office environments as needed by the company.

# Skills

- HTML
- CSS
- JavaScript
- Java
- PHP

- Flutter
- Svelte
- Laravel
- Tailwind
- Bootstrap

- Express.js
- Node.js
- MongoDB
- MySQL
- Git

# **Experience**

# R17 Group (Jakarta, Indonesia)

Software Developer (May 2021-April 2023)

- Implemented websites, mobile applications, and landing pages from concept through deployment
- Effectively translated client requirements into application designs and systems requirements

#### Smart Computerindo (Jakarta, Indonesia)

Front-End Web Developer (January 2021-July 2021)

- Implemented websites and landing pages according to design
- Collaborated with product team members to implement new feature developments

# Glolingo Indonesia (Malang, Indonesia)

Web Developer (September 2020-November 2020)

- Maintaining, optimizing, troubleshooting, and improving websites
- Report progress every week

# **Education**

# Brawijaya University (2017-2023)

Bachelor of Informatics Engineering - GPA 3,58

# **Licenses and Certifications**

- Get Started with Programming Fundamentals to Become a Software Developer | Dicoding
- Pursue a Career as a Software Developer | Dicoding
- Learn SOLID Programming Principles | Dicoding
- Learn Git Basics with GitHub | Dicoding